okay this video has to be made I'm sorry
I can't help myself I was right and I
was right more than five four or five
years ago so it's become really popular
to slam on Rust and talk about how come
developers hate it and you do a little
search about rust about rust being slow
and you can find all of these videos of
people you know within the last year
jumping on it including Theo and Prime
and he's gone back and forth and loving
hating it and all these other people
bringing up their things about why they
love it and stuff and by the way the
conversations are's Prime by the way and
you know it's it's all the same thing
but then my humble little stupid video
which actually got me death threats
during the the time of the 2016 election
I think they were jokes but I'm not
kidding I can show you and uh my little
video that I made 4 years ago which
garnered the attention of entire reddish
subgroup just my video by the way was
much more respectful I was frustrated
but I was respectful all these other
videos that are like hating on Rust and
stuff now they're nowhere near as
respectful as mine was and yet and I was
the only person coding go four years ago
on Twitch the only person literally the
only one and I had to put up with
all the time about people saying why
aren't you coding in Rust it's better
than everything and I was and I got
tired of it but I kept asking the
question I actually tried to use it got
really frustrated by how horrible it was
for all the reasons that are well well
documented in these other videos that
have far more views than I than mine do
mine are the same reasons in fact I kind
of wonder if these other video people
watched my video to summarize because
their summaries are exactly the same go
make your own conclusions you know what
I don't need to be right all the time
but sometimes I do and given the amount
of that I took over this video and
getting branded this anti-rust
and having all of the problems that I
did four and a half years ago and now
watching all of those people all of
those major streamers all those major
YouTubers all those major developers now
doing go instead I was right that's all